Curriculum Vitae Yifan (Daniel) Wang

Personal Information

ADDRESS: Professor de Moorplein 48, 5037DN, Tilburg, The Netherlands

PHONE: +31 639821663

E-MAIL: daniel.y.wang95@gmail.com

Professional Profile

A development enthusiast with work experiences in multiple sustainable development goals. An effective communicator with cultural awareness and ability to relate to diverse population with multiple cultural backgrounds. An experienced data analyzer in both quantitative and qualitative data analysis. A fast self-learner.

Education

Sept. 2018- Current M.S.c Global Prosperity, University College London, GB

Expected Graduation Date: Aug. 2019

This Master Program covers some alternative solutions towards some of the urgent global problems, such as sustainable food procurement, urban planning and smart cities, as well as financialization around the world.

B.S.c Global Management of Social Issues, Tilburg University, NL Sept. 2015- Sept. 2018

> This undergraduate program covers a great variety of topics includes Economics (Macro), Finance Management (Accounting), Advanced Project Management (Stakeholder Management, WBS), Statistics (Questionnaire, Causal Analysis, SPSS and Nvivo Practicals), Human Resource Management (Cross-cultural HRM, Strategic HRM).

Achievements:

- Winner of GMSI Scholarship awarded by Tilburg University from Study Year 2015- 2018(€ 30,000)
- Excellent Bachelor Thesis: Grade: 9/10

International Organization

Employment

DEC 2017

United Nations, Palais des Nations, Geneva, Switzerland

FEB 2018

Role:Intern

Field: Communication (40 hours per week)

- •Collect, verify, categorize, disseminate, and archive over 500 news daily related to UNECE, make sure other departments have clear reference point for their project coverage.
- •Optimize daily news brief under the instruction of the supervisor.
- •Coordinate the proposal of increasing UNECE's social media exposure in China, conduct preliminary research, contact other UN stakeholders and provide feedback to supervisor for reference.
- Create original content for all UNECE's social media, conduct monthly and annually social media performance analysis.
- •Train new interns on site and work together to build an intern team.
- Other ad-hoc events such as publishing PR releases and taking photos at meetings.

AUG 2017

IRC, The Hague, The Netherlands

NOV 2017

Non-governmental Organization Role: Intern Field: Innovation & Information (40 hours per week)

- •Summarize IRC's history in the last 50 years from its annual reports.
- •Research on grey literatures. Contact with senior employees, WASH (Water Hygiene and Sanitation) NGOs, and UN agencies for the retrieval of the organization's history; record, sort and summarize their verbal accounts as supplements to annual reports.
- •Completed the first version of IRC's Wikipedia Page based on the information gathered.
- •Write a webpage for IRC's 50-year history exhibition and create IRC's 50-year anniversary's event calendar.
- •Help with the data entry and cleaning from IRC's own project as well as a project from its partner organization, Agua Consult.
- •Propose a way to design a hygiene effectiveness ladder.
- •Write two working papers on the design of hygiene effectiveness ladder and a lightweight analysis platform as internship assignment.

Software

IBM SPSS Intermediate level
Gantt Project Intermediate Level

Nivivo Intermediate level

Bracket Entry level ArcGIS Entry Level

Volunteer

APR. 2019 - Current

Out & Abroad

LGBTQA+

The Hague, The Netherlands

Non-for-Profit Organization

Role: Event coordinator & influencer

Responsible for spreading the organization's influence. Provided edit suggestions to PR releases, social media posts and activities proposal. Co-hosted social events and helped on other ad-hoc tasks.

OCT 2015 - MAR 2017

Stichting Handao School

Education

Amersfoort, The Netherlands

Non-for-Profit Organization

Role: Teacher

The main instruction languages were Dutch and Chinese. Taught Chinese language and Chinese culture to Dutch K-12 students. I developed a strong bond with my students in the past two years. Received a lot of positive remarks from parents and colleagues throughout my teaching processes.

Languages

ENGLISH C3

CHINESE

Native

DUTCH **B1** (Waiting for **B2** certificate)